<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_US"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_US" /><updated>2025-08-04T22:07:26-07:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">HPAA - Hot Pot Astronomical Association</title><subtitle>Hot Pot Astronomical Association (HPAA) is a Chinese astronomy enthusiasts  organization in the San Francisco Bay Area. We enjoy astronomy and life under  the dark California sky, looking up at the universe while enjoying hot pot below.</subtitle><author><name>HPAA Team</name></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome to HPAA - Hot Pot Astronomical Association</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/welcome-to-hpaa/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to HPAA - Hot Pot Astronomical Association" /><published>2024-01-15T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2024-01-15T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/welcome-to-hpaa</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/welcome-to-hpaa/"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the official website of the <strong>Hot Pot Astronomical Association (HPAA)</strong>! We’re excited to share our passion for astronomy and hot pot culture with the world.</p>

<h2 id="our-story">Our Story</h2>

<p>The name ‘hot pot’ originates from 2017 CalStar in Whisper Canyon, where we cooked Chinese hot pot under the stars. The universe was born in a hot dense soup, and we believe the sky with all kinds of galaxies/nebulae/stars is just like the hot pot with different food inside.</p>

<p>火锅天文协会(HPAA)，是旧金山湾区的一个华人天文爱好者组织。宇宙诞生于一团热汤之中，就好像我们的火锅。我们在加州黑暗的天空下，抬头看宇宙，低头吃火锅，享受天文，享受生活。</p>

<h2 id="what-we-do">What We Do</h2>

<p>HPAA is a Chinese astronomy enthusiasts organization in the San Francisco Bay Area. We enjoy astronomy and life under the dark California sky, looking up at the universe while enjoying hot pot below.</p>

<h3 id="our-activities-include">Our Activities Include:</h3>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Stargazing Events</strong>: Regular meetups under the dark California sky</li>
  <li><strong>Hot Pot Gatherings</strong>: Sharing meals while discussing astronomical discoveries</li>
  <li><strong>Educational Workshops</strong>: Learning about telescopes, astrophotography, and celestial objects</li>
  <li><strong>Community Building</strong>: Connecting Chinese astronomy enthusiasts in the Bay Area</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="join-our-community">Join Our Community</h2>

<p>Whether you’re an experienced astronomer or just starting your journey into the cosmos, HPAA welcomes all enthusiasts. Our community values:</p>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Inclusivity</strong>: All experience levels welcome</li>
  <li><strong>Cultural Connection</strong>: Bridging astronomy and Chinese hot pot culture</li>
  <li><strong>Learning</strong>: Sharing knowledge and experiences</li>
  <li><strong>Friendship</strong>: Building lasting connections under the stars</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="upcoming-events">Upcoming Events</h2>

<p>Stay tuned for our upcoming events:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Monthly stargazing sessions</li>
  <li>Hot pot meetups</li>
  <li>Telescope workshops</li>
  <li>Astrophotography sessions</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="get-in-touch">Get in Touch</h2>

<p>Ready to join us? Contact us through our website or follow us on social media for the latest updates and event announcements.</p>

<p><em>Looking up at the universe while enjoying hot pot below</em><br />
抬头看宇宙，低头吃火锅</p>]]></content><author><name>HPAA Team</name></author><category term="welcome" /><category term="astronomy" /><category term="hot-pot" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the official website of HPAA! Learn about our mission to bring together astronomy enthusiasts while enjoying the warmth of hot pot culture.]]></summary></entry></feed>